<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Sassy DC - Links</title>
		<description>A monthly meetup in Washington, DC to discuss the latest in Sass, Compass, and Front End Dev</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.links.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Sass Hack Night</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an open hack night! Get guidance while exploring the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sass-lang.com/&quot;&gt;Sass language&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;http://sassmeister.com/&quot;&gt;Sassmeister&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://codepen.io/&quot;&gt;Codepen&lt;/a&gt;, recieve help with getting Sass or &lt;a href=&quot;http://libsass.com/&quot;&gt;Libsass&lt;/a&gt; compiling on your own computer, or put your head together with others to crack a particularly challenging Sass nut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send a note to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/dcsassmeetup&quot;&gt;@dcsassmeetup&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dcsassmeetup@gmail.com&quot;&gt;dcsassmeetup@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; if you&amp;#39;d like to request specific help in advance or volunteer to be a tutor so we can make sure we have a good match of skill sets.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/hack-night.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Beyond Keyframes: Modern web animation techniques</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;A non-dogmatic look at the place of CSS in web animation and how you can leverage javascript to easily produce crisp, flexible UI animations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Eli Fitch&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eli is a developer at ISL who loves crafting unforgettable experiences, animations, and applications that track beer inventory and temperature.  He is capable of communicating solely in gifs and dreams of one day chasing a man atop a moving train.  You can find him on &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/elifitch&quot;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/elifitch&quot;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://codepen.io/EliFitch&quot;&gt;codepen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/animation.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Intro to Mapbox Studio</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to design a beautiful custom map for your next website or app! We&amp;#39;ll walk through the whole process – from data to live map – using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mapbox.com/mapbox-studio/&quot;&gt;Mapbox Studio&lt;/a&gt;, a new map design tool. We&amp;#39;ll also take a closer look at styling in Mapbox Studio with CartoCSS, a language based on CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Nicki Dlugash&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mapbox.com/about/team/#nicki-dlugash&quot;&gt;Nicki&lt;/a&gt; is a designer and cartographer at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mapbox.com/&quot;&gt;Mapbox&lt;/a&gt;, where she splits her time between making maps and making tools to help others make maps.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/intro-to-mapbox.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Building The CustomInk Living Style Guide</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for a lively group discussion and bring your A-game of questions as we talk about our process and technical building blocks for our new living style guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Existing framework or building new.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grid choices galore.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Style guides as communication tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ken Collins&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby, JavaScript, Sass, iOS. Stinky Cheese &amp;amp; Beer Advocate. Working at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customink.com/&quot;&gt;CustomInk&lt;/a&gt; and loving it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Jonathan Lehman&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Software Engineer at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.customink.com/&quot;&gt;CustomInk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>voxmedia.com</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/building-customink-styleguide.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Gulp, NPM, and you.</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;How to take &lt;a href=&quot;http://gulpjs.com/&quot;&gt;Gulp&lt;/a&gt; to the next level with cross-device syncing, smarter code compiling, image optimization, and custom templating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Tommy Marshall&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tommy has been a Front-end Developer at Viget for over two and a half years. While at Viget he has worked with clients such as PUMA, Dick&amp;#39;s Sporting Goods, and OPower, and on projects like ESPN&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://espn.go.com/mlb/techniques/pitchanatomy/&quot;&gt;Anatomy of a Pitch&lt;/a&gt; and Viget&amp;#39;s own &lt;a href=&quot;http://sayviget.com/&quot;&gt;SayViget.com&lt;/a&gt;. Outside of coding he enjoys home brewing, playing guitar poorly, and getting the most out of his Amazon prime account. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/gulp-npm-and-you.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Sass 102</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Sure, you fell in love with Sass when you wrote your first variable, saved gobs of time by nesting your selectors, and maybe even wrote a mixin or two. But there&amp;#39;s so much more that Sass can do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this talk, we&amp;#39;ll go through what makes Sass more of a real programming language: data types and control structures. We&amp;#39;ll look through lists, looping and even the new Sass &amp;quot;maps&amp;quot; data type in version 3.3, along some real-world examples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Tracy Rotton&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.taupecat.com/&quot;&gt;Tracy Rotton&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/taupecat&quot;&gt;@taupecat&lt;/a&gt;) is the Lead Web Developer at RP3 Agency specializing in front end, WordPress and responsive development. She has spoken at WordCamps in Baltimore (and soon in Miami and Philadelphia as well), and was a recent guest on the Shop Talk Show podcast. She&amp;#39;s also writing a book on building responsive WordPress themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When not doing web things, you can find Tracy skiing, rooting for her Washington Redskins, or spending time with her two kids.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/Sass-102.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Say Yes to Yeoman!</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Yeoman is a set of tools and conventions for developing client side web applications. It combines three of the most popular front-end workflow tools: Grunt (for automation), Bower(for package management), and Yo (for scaffolding boilerplate code). We’ll take a high level look at what these tools do and how they can improve your everyday development process — lots of concept, not too much code! We’ll also examine how Yeoman and the projects around it are becoming concentrations of best practices and developer knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robert Wierzbowski works at Think Through Math, where he specializes in front-end development and build systems. He spends way too much time working on open source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow him on Twitter at @robwierzbowski&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/yo-yeoman.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Managing Responsive Image Display with Sass</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Sass can&amp;#39;t help you swap out image sources, but it can be incredibly helpful in managing display variations across different screen sizes. Using real life examples from building the redesign of National Geographic Magazine we&amp;#39;ll work our way from assessing the challenges to how using variables, mixins, and placeholder classes will keep your source code organized, extensible, and—most importantly—manageable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://nvite.com/sassydc/feb2014&quot;&gt;nvite.com/sassydc/feb2014&lt;/a&gt; to sign up!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/managing-responsive-images-with-sass.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>Perspectives on File Structure</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Organizing a project&amp;#39;s file structure is the first step to maximizing its efficiency while working on it. This is a subject that causes much debate because there isn&amp;#39;t really one solid method that is optimized for every scenario. This presentation explores various file organization approaches based on project depth and team size.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/perspectives-on-file-structure.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
			
			<item>
				<title>What&#39;s New in Sass 3.3?</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;For our inaugural meetup we&amp;#39;ll be exploring the the new features available in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SassCSS/status/389086335505805312&quot;&gt;current release candidate&lt;/a&gt; version of Sass.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://canvas.co/work</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/whats-new-in-sass-3-3.html</guid>
			</item>
			
		
	</channel>
</rss>
